[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["U.S."]}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", ":", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 11, "question": "What do we know, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 12, "answer": "We know that the U.S. has been on a heightened state of alert, Piers, for some time now, specifically -- specifically because on Sunday is the 10th anniversary of 9/11.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "What can you tell me about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "I do know that that is taking place, obviously, in New York, not here, not involving the White House.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "But have you seen anything quite like this in terms of the warning they have given, the strength of the warning, the number of official bodies coming out now making statements, briefings and so on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "I haven't seen anything exactly like this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["1 percent"]}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "CC", "JJR", ",", "RB", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "What is your reaction and do you think he'll get this through?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Well, we certainly need to deal with the sinking economy, the growth that we're seeing now is 1 percent or less, far below what was projected just a few months ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this morning"]}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "What do you know about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Well, I know that the president was briefed first thing this morning.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "What makes you taking this one so seriously?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "CD", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "The president takes all threats to our country very seriously, and that's why he's asked his team to redouble our efforts.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "What do you think his reaction is now that he's made it to the early reaction you've been receiving to the speech?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "Well, I think that he's received a lot of very positive reaction to the speech.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CC", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "If it doesn't work, if we get to next summer and unemployment has continued to rise, would you as the administration accept that the American public would have a right to vote the president out of office?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Look, this isn't a matter of the president in or out of office.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["summer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Are you encouraged by their reaction or do you think you may be facing a pretty uphill battle here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "Well, no, we're encouraged.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "Is it going to work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Well, I think it's significant, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "I mean, is this going to actually make a big enough difference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "I think it will make a big difference.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "And if so, in what kind of time scale?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "RB", ",", "IN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "It feels to me like this is more kind of spurring demand in the short term.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "What did you make of his ambitious plans of America to stop being the world's biggest consumer and perhaps go back to what they used to be really good at, which is become one of the world's great producers and manufacturers again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "POS", "JJS", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "RB", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Well, I think that's what we need to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Ron Paul, what do you make of it, not very impressed then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "No, not too much.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ron Paul"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "The country may not have much money, but he's got to do something, doesn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "Well, you know, I think you state the problem that we have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Mr. Brinkley, your reaction to the jobs speech tonight, please?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Well, I think it was -- the president was trying to give a jolt to the economy.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Brinkley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "Should he have really gone for it, put a trillion dollars behind this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Well, I don't think a trillion dollars would have been credible.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["trillion dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "How credible does it sound to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Well, the phraseology you talk about is specific, credible and unconfirmed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York", "Washington"]}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "What are you expecting from this press conference that we're going to get to in a moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "What I've heard of the threat -- I actually heard it was New York or Washington.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Mayor"]}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "Jane?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "Thank you, Mr. Mayor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Mayor"]}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Ray?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Thank you, Mr. Mayor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "Mr. Mayor?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "Commissioner, thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Bloomberg"]}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Can you tell us what forced your hand to make this now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "That's Michael Bloomberg there in a press conference about the terror threat tonight, which is believed to be involving the tenth anniversary of 9/11.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "What was your view when you heard the comments they made?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "I think that they are using measured language, which is meant to inspire people to pay attention and to report what they see because of a heightened threat picture, but also very measured language not to cause overdue concern or panic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Susan, what is the latest information you have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "The latest information, Piers, is that three people might possibly be involved.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Are you happy about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Dave Ramsey, would you agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Absolutely, I would agree with that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dave Ramsey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Do you actually believe that what the president outlined today is going to stimulate the jobs market enough to make any substantial difference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Well, I don't, because what comes with this is the ticket that we go further into debt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110908pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "CD", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Back to CNN's Susan Candiotti now with the latest breaking news on the terror threat against New York and D.C. Susan, what have you got?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Certainly these are two areas that already on edge with the anniversary of 9/11, the tenth anniversary rolling around.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CNN"], "LOCATION": ["New York"], "PERSON": ["Susan Candiotti", "D.C. Susan"]}}]